Guide to the Samuel Shaffer papers, 1948-1982 MS2091
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Chronological files, 1948-1976; MS2091 Series 1; 17 Linear feet
  - Chronological files, 1956 (Box 7, Folder 3)
    [from original finding aid] Newsmakers from Shaffer; Foreign - Willey - from Shaffer; Scoop Jackson and the ballistics missile; Re No.3 of 01/19/1956; Correction (N-23-Gas); Maggie Smith; Ridgway; The Dulles article and Congress; The Democratic Dilemma--Kefauver Story; Gas Investigation; Add to Dulles memo; Dulles; Farm Bill; S-14 Congress; Memo on lobby inquiry (to supplement clips); Congress (special section)
  - Chronological files, 1956 (Box 7, Folder 4)
    [from original finding aid] Nation from Shaffer; The lobby inquiry; Rep.Jackson's poetry of indignation; Farm bill; N-16-Farm; Lobbies; Nation (Lavine) from Shaffer; Congress Week, continued; Congress Week, continued (page seven); Add to Farm Bill memo; N-16-Farm; Congress Week; Conway Biz from Shaffer (highway); Cleaton from Shaffer (Farm legislation); Biz from Shaffer; Congress Week, continued (page six); Congress Week (farm bill); N14 Dems
  - Chronological files, 1956 (Box 7, Folder 5)
    [from original finding aid] Re the Case Incident; Sen.Green; Congress Roundup; Congress Week; Congress Week, continued (page eight)(Congress; and CIA); Congress Week/ concluded (page 12) Re the farm bill veto; Washn trends from Shaffer (Symington Investigation) Soil bank New lead trends The Senate races
  - Chronological files, 1956 (Box 7, Folder 6)
    [from original finding aid] Wash trends from Staffer; Congress Week (taxes); Congress Week, continued (page five) (Farm Bill); Congress Week, continued (page nine) (Murray Chotiner); Wash trends; Wash trends with Shaffer, Weintal, Lindley - page six; 7-; Barbi from Shaffer; N-16-Taxes; N-20-Chotiner; Congress Week Taxes; Congress and Foreign Aid; Chotiner; (Harris); Nation from Shaffer; Washington trends from Shaffer, Davis, Salisbury, Madigan; Lausche quotes for a box on what Lausche believes; Suggested precede Lausche story; Lausche
  - Chronological files, 1956 (Box 7, Folder 7)
    [from original finding aid] Wash trends from Shaffer, Davis, Weintal, Roberts; Washington Trends from Shaffer 05/12/1956; Congress Week, continued (page 12) (Murray Chotiner); Civil Rights; Congress Week (Civil Rights); Where the Candidates stand now; Symington Memo (Message #2 of 06/06/1956); Congress Week (Foreign Aid Bill); Congress Week, continued (page nine)(Social Security); Congress Week, concluded (page twelve) (Fred Seaton's; confirmation); Your No.l of 06/09/1956 (Symington) Political consequences of Ike's illness 5-Shaffer (Republican reaction to Ike's illness)
  - Chronological files, 1956 (Box 7, Folder 8)
    [from original finding aid] Foreign Aid; Query No.2; Conway from Shaffer-06/15/1956; N-18-Democrats; Mac Muir from Crawford; Muir from Crawford; Washington Trends; To Nation Fishkin; Congress Week (Charlie Wilson's blunder); Biz Trends 06/22/1956; Nation from Washington 06/23/1955; Lavine from Washington; Foreign Aid Debate; Stevenson's Running Mate
  - Chronological files, 1956 (Box 7, Folder 9)
    [from original finding aid] The Democratic Platform; Blue copy Pre 32 Estes; Kefauver bows out; Tinkham; Alsop polling tour; The primaries; Rayburn; Religion from Shaffer-09/12/1956 Pennsylvania; Query No.3 09/27/1956; Query No.5 9/27/56
  - Chronological files, 1956 (Box 7, Folder 10)
    [from original finding aid] Washington Trends; For trends; Nation, Wash Trends from Toledano (Nixon); Press from Tait (query #1, 10/05/1956); Memo--where campaign stands today 10/05/1956; Mary Pope from Shaffer (Kennedy); Kefauver and the Senate; Alaska; For trends; The Truth Squad - memo; Nation (Lavine) from Shaffer - Toledano; Nation (election extra) from Shaffer; (The Senate); 6-; Election impact on business; Republican Congressional losses; Lavine from Shaffer (switches); Trouble on the foreign policy front; Presidential Conference (ME)
  - Chronological files, 1956 (Box 7, Folder 11)
    [from original finding aid] Two-Party South; N-15; Congress - the liberal revolt; Nation from Shaffer; For trends (Civil Rights legislation); Republican post mortem; The Democrats and foreign policy; Wash Trends; Nation from Shaffer 12/01/1956 (excerpts from a; letter sent by Rep Francis Walter to Brownell; and Dulles) Democrats Memo on Sen Green; N-16 Dems; For trends (civil/legislation); Education from Shaffer (Re your #5 of 12/12/1956); Wash. trends; Hams; Washington Trends; The Conference Chairmanship; For Wash Trends (School problems) 12/21/1956; Outlook special session - Congress; Congress
  - Chronological files, 1957 (Box 8, Folder 1)
    [from original finding aid] The Mideast resolution Your No.7 of 01/15/1957 (Launches); Wash. Trends (revolt against Sen. Lyndon Johnson) Filibuster; Lausche and the organization of the Senate Congress Week; Congress Week, continued (page 7) Congress Week, continued (page 14) Congress Week, continued (page 16) Wash Trends (Knowland) More Washington trends (civil rights) For Wash trends (1/12/57); Congress Week, continued (page 21) (The Mideast Resolution)
  - Chronological files, 1957 (Box 8, Folder 2)
    [from original finding aid] The Mideast resolution; Nation from Shaffer (budget); Highway program; Breakdown; For Wash trends (Dulles, Natural Gas); Congressional Reaction on Humphrey; Mideast resolution; Civil Rights; Symington Report (American Air Power)
  - Chronological files, 1957 (Box 8, Folder 3)
    [from original finding aid] For Wash trends (AEA); Henry Ford's speech; Mideast resolution; For Wash. trends (Labor Racketeering Investigation;; Alaska Statehood); For Wash. trends (Eisenhower Doc.); Washington Trends (Drive f.Dem. Sen '69; Civil Rights) A break for ex-presidents Foreign aid; For Washington Only (Oil) Oil Investigations; For. Wash. trends (a new crisis; German Unity) Mail
  - Chronological files, 1957 (Box 8, Folder 4)
    [from original finding aid] The Smathers Bill; Mideast resolution; White House aides; Congress and the Israeli Crisis; Highway deaths; Ike's legislative aides; For Wash. trends (Ike's invincibility..., Nixon); Wash. trends (Johnson's emerging role, airline; routes); Nation from Shaffer-02/28/1957; Nation (Lavine) from Shaffer (Eisenhower Doc) Eisenhower Doctrine--page eight The Eisenhower Doctrine and Sanctions History of Presidential breaks with Congress
  - Chronological files, 1957 (Box 8, Folder 5)
    [from original finding aid] Add to Congress Memo; Civil Rights; Mideast resolution finale; Add Wash. trends (Small Business Investigations); For Wash. trends (Politics; the Republican prob); For Wash. trends (Democratic fears; the counter attack); Add Texas memo; Query No.5 of 3-12 (budget); Texas and the Senate; For Wash. trends (Humphrey; Dulles; decline and fall;; labor investigations); Budget cuts and tax relief - the Democratic dilemma Labor and politics For Wash. trends (foreign policy; civil rights; farm; legislation; airline route fight; scientific; scholarships) Add at end of budget, economy and taxes
  - Chronological files, 1957 (Box 8, Folder 6)
    [from original finding aid] The budget, economy and taxes; The Bermuda conference-The White House briefing; The Beal book (Aswan Dam); Lavine from Shaffer (budget); Congress-the economy drive and the story behind it; For Wash. trends (Texas election); More Wash. trends (Committee rumbles); Nation and copy desk form Shaffer (04/12/1957); For Wash. trends (Senate reform; Rackets Committee; A Reuther Investigation; Monetary Investigation; end of farm bloc); Nation from Shaffer 04/12/1957 (appropriation bills); Interview with Senator Richard L. Neuberger on federal contributions to political campaigns; Congress Week (Sen. Barry Goldwater)
  - Chronological files, 1957 (Box 8, Folder 7)
    [from original finding aid] British loan debate; Congress, Ike, and the budget; For Wash. trends; For Wash. trends (Civil Rights; agriculture); Medicine from Shaffer-05/01/1957; McLeod; The budget fight; For Wash. trends; Your telephonic to Ives; Congress Week (Foreign aid and the economy fight); Congress Week, continued-page eight (Right to Work); Congress Week, continued-page 9; Congress Week, continued-page twelve; Congress Week, concluded--page fourteen; Congress Week (Budget)
  - Chronological files, 1957 (Box 8, Folder 8)
    [from original finding aid] Congress Week, continued-page nine (the Soil Bank); Wash. Trends (Lame Duck Amendment); Congress Week, concluded (page fourteen) Morse and Ike); Congress Week, continued (page seven) (Foreign Aid); Congress Week (Battle of the budget); Adams; For. Wash. trends (economy); Religion from Shaffer (Yes it is); Congress cuts defense; For. Wash. trends (Welfare Fund Legislation); More Wash. trends (Hell Canyon Dam); Welfare Fund Legislation; More Wash. trends (Mid-East proposals)
  - Chronological files, 1957 (Box 8, Folder 9)
    [from original finding aid] Isolationism and the South; N-21-Girard; Congress Week (China Trade); Congress Week, continued (page four) (Girard case and; the Status of Forces Agreements); Congress Week, continued (page nine)(Civil Rights) Congress Week, concluded (page fifteen) (Agriculture; -end of the farm bloc); Washington Trends (Executive Agreements) Wash. Trends (Democrats on Propaganda) Civil Rights; Congress Week, continued-page nine (Agriculture Bill) Congress Week (Troubles plague the Democrats in Civil; Rights and Agriculture) Was,h. Trends (Ike and Congress)
  - Chronological files, 1957 (Box 8, Folder 10)
    [from original finding aid] Nation from Shaffer 06/21/1957 (Supreme Court; and Congress) More Wash. trends; Wash. trends (Hells Canyon); Congressional investigations and the Supreme Court; Hells Canyon; Nation from Shaffer (Hells Canyon); Civil Rights; TV-Radio from Shaffer 06/26/1957 (Query #3); Foreign from Shaffer (Disarmament); Status of forces; Congress and the Supreme Court; Hoover Commission Progress; Disarmament
  - Chronological files, 1957 (Box 8, Folder 11)
    [from original finding aid] Girard case; Nation from Shaffer (Sen.Karl E. Mundt); Wash. Trends (Kennedy Boom); Wash. Trends (Defense Spending); Congress Week (Girard Case); Taxes; Girard Case and the Bow Amendments; Wash. trends (Senate); The McClellan Committee "Love Feast"; Add to Civil Rights memo; Congress Week (Civil Rights); Lavine from Shaffer 07/04/1957 (Per telephone request); Civil Rights
  - Chronological files, 1957 (Box 8, Folder 12)
    [from original finding aid] Congress Week (page six) (Civil Rights) (07/12/1957); Civil Rights; Wash. trends (Tax cuts 11/1958?); N-11-Rights; Wash. Trends (alien Assets); Wash. Trends (Union Curbs); Wash. Trends (Negro Vote); Wash. Trends (Alaska); Wash. Trends (Senate Turnover); Civil Rights; The School Bill; Wash. Trends (investigations Scandal); Wash. Trends (Gas Bill); N-19-Civil Rights Civil Rights
  - Chronological files, 1957 (Box 9, Folder 1)
    [from original finding aid] Alaska; Periscope; 3-; Wash. Trends (Foreign Aid); Wash. Trends ("Deductible" bribes); For Wash. trends (Outlook for Ike); Political Consequences of the Arkansas crisis; Wash. Trends (Trouble for Benson); Periscope from Shaffer; Wash. trends (Ike Republicans); Wash. trends (Spending holddown); Wash. trends (Reciprocal Trade); Brook Hays; Politics; Political consequences; Nation (Ike in use of troops); Nation from Shaffer (Sen. Richard Russell); Wash. trends (Will Knowland step down?); Statement of Sen.Stuart Symington, of Missouri; Wash. Trends (Benson again); Wash. Trends (No. Rules change); Wash. Trends (A Civil Rights Commission?); Cannon from Shaffer (Little Rock); Faubus
  - Chronological files, 1957 (Box 9, Folder 2)
    [from original finding aid] Wash. trends (Rackets Committee; Budget Bureau); The NAACP as a lobby; Labor legislation; Wash. trends; Wash. trends (Kennedy); Wash. Trends (Strom Thurmond); Wash. Trends (Smather's bill); Wash. Trends (Congress and the satellite); The Race for Space; The Sputnik, Congress, and politics; Wash. trends (Ike's troubles); 2- (Ike Republicans); 3-; 4-; The Sputnik and Congress; Wash. Trends (Sputnik aftermath); Wash. trends (Ike and Congress); Brownell; Ike and Congress; Nation from Shaffer 10/24/1957 (Knowland); Biz from Shaffer; Science from Shaffer (Congressional comments on; Soviet Science (10/30/1957)) From Shaffer (Nuclear cooperation) From Shaffer From Shaffer From Shaffer
  - Chronological files, 1957 (Box 9, Folder 3)
    [from original finding aid] Democratic possibilities; Add to election impact story; Election impact; Wash. Trends (sharing secrets status of forces;; Sputnik issue; Reuther investigation; Benson;; Little Rock) Missile investigation Press from Shaffer (Maggie Higgins) Wash. trends (GOP rumbles) Coalition revived --P-13 Higgins Missile program No. 3 Washington Crawford from Lavine (Among the questions Ike's speech raised)
  - Chronological files, 1957 (Box 9, Folder 4)
    [from original finding aid] Wash. trends (labor legislation) Scientists in government Ike's speech; Nation from Shaffer 11/15/1957 (Sharing Atomic Secrets); Press from Shaffer (Maggie Higgins); Nation from Shaffer 11/19/1957 (Congressional Consensus); Succession (Nixon); Wash. trends (Succession legislation); Wash. trends (Nixon and Knowland); Wash. trends (Symington and Johnson); Nation from Shafffer-11/22/1957 (Add to missiles; investigation memo) The Missiles investigation Labor legislation
  - Chronological files, 1957 (Box 9, Folder 5)
    [from original finding aid] Wash. trends (Prestige race; school bills); Congress; Nation from Shaffer (Exclusive statement., by Sen. Joseph O'Mahoney); The secret testimony (exclusive); Nation from Shaffer and Ives ( Benson ); Washington Trends; From Salisbury (The Atom); From Salisbury (Education Bill); From Wyden (GOP Worries); From Davis ( Army/Missiles ); Washington trends (from Shaffer) Political Outlook; From Volkov Tito; From Weintal (mideast problem); From Shaffer (Farm program); Nation from Shaffer (add to Ike's troubles)
  - Chronological files, 1957 (Box 9, Folder 6)
    [from original finding aid] Food and bureaucracy-exclusive; The Great Debate; Wash. trends (Reuther inquiry;); Missile politics; Wilbur Mills; Add to violin memo; For violin; Congressional consensus story; Wash. trends (Conservative coalition); 2-traffic safety drive; Predictions (Administration; Politics); Biz Trends; Legislation roundup (taxes; Health and Welfare Pension; Funds; Labor Legislation; Agriculture; Anti-trust) Wash. trends (Trading) Wash. trends (Integration)
  - Chronological files, 1958 (Box 10, Folder 1)
    [from original finding aid] The State of the Union Message; GOP revolt; Wash. Trends (Regulating commissions;); Wash. Trends (School bill); Wash. Trends (Politics); N-25 Succession; Wash. Trends (farm legislation; natural gas); Benson and the farm state vote; My memo on Benson and Farm State Vote; Correction; Benson; Add to Benson memo; The Benson memo; The Benson showdown; Nation from Shaffer-Crawford (Benson); Biz (Chappell) from Shaffer (Railroad query 01/08/1958); Wash. trends (Presidential disability); Wash. trends (Polaris); Wash. trends (foreign policy); Wash. trends (Pentagon Reorganization)
  - Chronological files, 1958 (Box 10, Folder 2)
    [from original finding aid] Lewis Strauss; Add from Crawford (Congressional Revolt); Press from Shaffer (Texas observer query); Wash. trends (defense politics); Wash. trends (atomic truce); Wash. trends (Reciprocal trade troubles; Statehood; outlook (Hawaii); Kickbacks outlawed; Foreign; aid loans; Wash. trends (Civil Rights; Gas Bill Troubles) Kickbacks (revised); Correction (Rep Oren Harris of Arkansas) Defense Inquiry; Nation from Shaffer 0l/17/1958 (listening post on Dulles) Ellender; Letter to Shaffer from Margeret Chase Smith Wash Trends (Spain); Nation from Shaffer (Updating memo on the Spanish ... food story); Missile politics; Pentagon Reorganization (in relation to Rockefeller; report); GOP politics and the satellite Wash. trends (missiles) Lyndon Johnson Add to Lyndon Johnson Another add Lyndon Johnson Insert Johnson Lavine from Shaffer
  - Chronological files, 1958 (Box 10, Folder 3)
    [from original finding aid] Natural gas bill; Labor Investigations and legislation; My Labor memo; The 8 points - what Congress will (Defense Reorganization ); Steel Investigation report; Labor legislation; Knowland; Nation from Shaffer and Salisbury Wash Trends (Nuclear Power); Biz 23-Snark; Wash. trends (Biological warfare; Reuther inquiry; Alaskan Statehood; GOP Patronage Complaints: Lyndon Johnson and the GOP); Tax cut (supplementing' Roweh); The gas bill (02/07/1958); The gas bill (2-14); Outer space control; Outer space showdown; Wash. trends (Martin-Halleck Feud); Wash. trends (Transport tax); Wash. trends (Monroney's aid proposal); Wash. trends (Reciprocal trade)
  - Chronological files, 1958 (Box 10, Folder 4)
    [from original finding aid] Business from Shaffer (Democratic tax plan); aggie Smith and the Texas Funds; Wash. trends (Disability legislation); Wash. trends (Catholics and politics); Wash. trends (FCC changes); Wash. trends (Alaska statehood, political advice); Nation from Shaffer 02/22/1958; Defense; The Reuther Inquiry; Presidential inability legislation; The Presidential inability stalemate; Senator Albert Gore (Tenn.), Senator Hubert H.; Humphrey (Minn.) Letter (Senator Kefauver) Senator J.F.Kennedy (Mass.) Senator Stuart Symington (Miss) Postoffice Modernization Political Economics; Nation from Shaffer, Rowen, Roberts (economic future) For the Ike package - The Democratic position Ike Section
  - Chronological files, 1958 (Box 10, Folder 5)
    [from original finding aid] Lyndon Johnson and recession; Republican woes and the recession; Recession politics; The budget bill; Senator Douglas (Statement for Newsweek); Senator Williams (Statement for Newsweek); Taxes and politicking; Labor; McClellan Committee; Periscope from Shaffer; N-16-Labor; Labor rackets report-exclusive; Disability (22 Mar 58); Republican farm revolt; Wash. trends (Senators to watch); Wash. trends (Congress and the Space Agency); Wash. trends (Taxes); Wash. trends (A rule change?); Wash. trends (Reciprocal trade); Wash. trends (School aid legislation); Lease-Purchase; For Wash. trends (farm legislation)
  - Chronological files, 1958 (Box 10, Folder 6)
    [from original finding aid] Farm vote; Billboards; Lavine from Shaffer 04/02/1958 (grass-roots sounding story); Defense reorganization and Congress; Lavine from Shaffer (Boiling); Kennedy and labor; Wash. trends (labor inquiry); Strauss--second thoughts on quitting; Benson and Congress; The last straw; Military reorganization and Congress (04/04/1958); Kennedy
  - Chronological files, 1958 (Box 10, Folder 7)
    [from original finding aid] Hal Lavine from Shaffer (Johnson's speech); Nation from Shaffer (Johnson's speech); Wash. trends (GOP strategy); Wash. trends (Dulles and Benson); Wash. trends (Congress outlook); Labor legislation; N-11-Violin; Liquor advertising debate; Butter, margerine, and the U.S.Navy; Wash. trends (social security expansion); Presidential Pensions; Defense Reorganization; 2-; The Flanagan Nomination; The states rights bill; Biz from Shaffer (Railroad bill); The reciprocal trade bill - No.3 on Shaffer's list; CIA--No.2 on Shaffer's story list; Nation from Shaffer (07/18/1958); Lebanon crisis--the White House meeting; The attack on the Supreme Court; Inside the Lebanon crisis
  - Chronological files, 1958 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Chronological files, 1958 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Chronological files, 1958 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Chronological files, 1958 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Chronological files, 1958 (Box 11, Folder 1)
    [from original finding aid] Labor legislation; Biz from Shaffer (Add taxes); The tax bill; Adam Reaction - Senate; Wash. trends (Foreign Aid Cut/Legislative record;); Wash. trends (China review; Vermont push; Dirksen as leader; labor politics; Supreme Court attack; ethics legislation); Wash. trends (Red China; Ike's Boner; school integration outlook); The labor issue; Taxes; Taxes; Alaska; Farm bill; The Butler-Jenner Bill; Kennedy labor bill; The labor bill story; Newsmaker from Shaffer (your No.3 query)(Boy Pages)
  - Chronological files, 1958 (Box 11, Folder 2)
    [from original finding aid] Humane slaughter; N-14-Slaughter; Foreign Aid; Lavine from Shaffer For Chart (07/24/1958)(Congressional; Box Score); Wash. Trends (Adams) Halleck; primary; social security; Supreme Court;; Space council Periscope from Shaffer The Three "musts" Nation (Estelle Whelan) from Shaffer (your query August; 29 on the Pension Disclosure Bill) The gravy train; Wash. trends (adjournment: Hawaii) Congress-the session roundup; 7-; 8-; 9-; Shaffer - page 10; Shaffer - page 11; Shaffer - page 12; The political season opens
  - Chronological files, 1958 (Box 11, Folder 3)
    [from original finding aid] Wash. trends (Nixon's optimism; Marine Corps: Filibusters; CIA; Iraqi outlook); Interpreting Maine; Politics (9/12); Politics. Our Memo No.9 of 9/12; 5-Shaffer (Foreign Policy and the campaign); GOP strategy; Johnson and Quemoy; Ethics legislation; Congress and Quemoy; Lavine from Shaffer 09/25/1958; Wash. trends from Shaffer (northern wing of Democratic Party; GOP squabble); Supreme Court Attack; 1960 Hopes; Quemoy outcome; Sherman Adams; Congress and the schools
  - Chronological files, 1958 (Box 11, Folder 4)
    [from original finding aid] Foreign policy and the campaign; Denson from Shaffer (The South Penn Co. Complaint); Silly Politics Query; Growing Political Power of the West; 3-Shaffer (Radio Spot No.4,5,7); Wash.trends (Alford contest; Halleck-Martin); Wash.trends(Thurmond); Wash.trends (Lame Ducks); Wash.trends (Ike Republicans); Wash.trends (Labor and Business in Politics); Periscope from Shaffer 11/15/1958; To: Periscope (Fulbright) from Shaffer (Query No.; one today); Wash.trends (taxes and aid) Ike and Congress; Biz from Shaffer (Smathers1 office) Lyndon Johnson (11/21/1958) Fulbright from Shaffer (your No.6) Nation from Shaffer (Note to Cannon) Wash.trends (liberal wing; labor rackets; labor; reform legislation; Alford contest; school; money; Catholic elections)
  - Chronological files, 1958 (Box 11, Folder 5)
    [from original finding aid] Interview with Sen.Talmadge, of Georgia (11-25); Filibuster curb; Space-Atom, Diamond Simmons 11/28/1958; The South in Congress (11/25/1958); Alaska (11-28); Wash.trends (The liberal Congress; Southern bitterness;; cabinet changes?) Wash.trends from Shaffer (Johnson on top; Alford; contest; labor domination; labor rackets; taxes; and aid; Supplementing the Southern political power memo (12-9) Southern memo Mills and taxes Morse-Neuberger feud
  - Chronological files, 1958 (Box 11, Folder 6)
    [from original finding aid] Wash. trends (Democratic Split?; Negro Unemployment); Democratic Committee and Quemoy issue Politics (Nixon) Adams; Wash. trends (A "new" Ike; Ike and schools: Ike and civil rights; McElroy Honeymoon over?;; Cancer tests; Supreme Court attack Some notes on Jerry Persons; Denson from Shaffer (Following is answer to Zehrung) Leadership problems in the new Congress; The Republicans and the 86th Congress The Democrats and the 86th Congress (LBJ) Wash.trends (taxes) Periscope from Shaffer; Problems of a lame duck president Wash.trends (Democratic Committee; Coalition outlook;labor spending; school money; Catholic elections) '60 Hopefuls Cannon from Shaffer (various Senate possibilities)
  - Chronological files, 1959 (Box 12, Folder 1)